http://www.goodgymguide.com.au/terms

Advertisement
Terms of Use
Privacy
1. Information We Collect and How We Use It
We may store the information you submit to or through the Site, as well as information that we collect in connection with your use of the Site.
We use the information to fulfil your requests, provide the Site’s functionality, improve the Site’s quality, personalise your experience, track usage of the Site, provide feedback to businesses that are listed on the Site, display relevant advertising, provide customer support, message you, back up our systems and allow for disaster recovery, enhance the security of the Site, and comply with legal obligations.
Among the information we collect, please note:
Account Information: If you create an account on Good Gym Guide, we may store and use your full name, email address, post code and other information you may provide with your account, such as your gender and birth date. Your first name and last name, as well as any photo you submit through the registration process, will be publicly displayed as part of your account profile only if you choose to publish your contact information. You can modify some of the information associated with your account here. If you feel that an unauthorised account has been created depicting you or your likeness, you can request its removal here.
Public Content: The information that you post to the Site is intended for public consumption, including your reviews, tips, photos, check-ins, comments, likes, Talk posts, bookmarks, friends, lists, compliments, and account profile. We may display this information on the Site, share it with businesses, and further distribute it to a wider audience through third party sites and services.
Communications: When you sign up for an account, you are opting in to receive emails from other Good Gym Guide users, businesses, and Good Gym Guide itself. You can manage your email preferences here, but note that you cannot opt out of receiving certain administrative or legal notices from Good Gym Guide. If you exchange messages with others through the Site, we may store them in order to process and deliver them, allow you to manage them, and investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site. If you send information from the Site to your phone via SMS text message, we may log your phone number, phone carrier, and the date and time that the message was processed. Carriers may charge recipients for texts that they receive.
Transactional Information: If you redeem deals through the Site, we may collect and store certain information about you to process your requests and populate forms for future transactions, such as your phone number, address and email address. This information may be shared with third parties who help process and fulfil your requests. If you write reviews about businesses with which you have redeemed deals, we may publicly display the fact that you communicated with those businesses.
Site Activity: We may store information about your use of the Site, such as your search activity, the pages you view, the date and time of your visit, and the businesses you call using our mobile applications. We also may store information that your computer or mobile device provides to us in connection with your use of the Site, such as your browser type, type of computer or mobile device, browser language, IP address, mobile carrier, unique device identifier, location, and requested and referring URLs.
2. Cookies
We, and third parties with whom we partner, may use cookies, web beacons, local shared objects (sometimes called "flash cookies"), and similar technology in connection with your use of the Site ("Cookies"). Cookies are small data files that may have unique identifiers, and reside, among other places, on your computer or mobile device, in emails we send to you, and on our web pages. Cookies may transmit information about you and your use of the Site, such as your browser type, search preferences, data relating to advertisements that have been displayed to you or that you have clicked on, and the date and time of your use. Cookies may be persistent or stored only during an individual session.
Types of Cookies used on the Site include:
Category of Use
Explanation
Processes
Intended to make the Site work in the way you expect it to. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have already signed up for an account.
Authentication, Security, and Compliance
Intended to prevent fraud, protect your data from unauthorised parties, and comply with legal requirements. For example, we use Cookies to determine if you are logged in.
Preferences
Intended to remember information about how you prefer the site to behave and look. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us whether you have declined to allow us to use your phone’s geolocation data.
Notifications
Intended to allow notice of information or options that we think could improve your use of the site. For example, we use a Cookie that allows us to stop showing you the signup notification if you have already seen it.
Advertising
Intended to make advertising more relevant to users and more valuable to advertisers. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us if you have recently clicked on an ad.
Analytics
Intended to help us understand how visitors use the Site. For example, we use a Cookie that tells us how our search suggestions correlate to your interaction with the search page.
Managing Cookies:
It may be possible to disable some (but not all) Cookies through your device or browser settings, but doing so may affect your ability to use the Site. The method for disabling cookies may vary by device and browser, but can usually be found in preferences or security settings.
3. Third Parties
We may share information about you with third parties as follows:
Advertisers: We may allow third parties to use Cookies on the Site to collect the same type of information for the same purposes as Good Gym Guide does for itself. They may be able to associate the information they collect with other information they have about you from other sources. We do not necessarily have access to or control over the Cookies they use, but you may be able to opt-out of some of their practices. Please note that opting out does not prevent the display of advertisements to you.
Service Providers: Some of the services that are offered through the Site, such as free gym passes or free personal training sessions, may be provided by third-party providers. We also outsource some of Good Gym Guide’s functions to third-party providers, such as technical and customer support, tracking and reporting functions, quality assurance, testing, payment processing functions, and other services. We may share information from or about you with these third-party providers so that they can perform their services or complete your requests.
Aggregate Information: We may share user information in the aggregate with third parties, such as advertisers and content distributors. For example, we may disclose the number of users that have been exposed to, or clicked on, advertisements.
Business Transfers: We may share information from or about you with subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honour this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires Good Gym Guide or all or substantially all of our assets, that company will possess the same information, and will assume the rights and obligations with respect to that information as described in this Privacy Policy.
Businesses on Good Gym Guide: We may share information from or about you (such as your age and gender) and your use of the Site (such as which businesses you bookmark or call) with businesses on Good Gym Guide. You may adjust your settings to increase or decrease the amount of information we share. You can view these settings and find more details about what information may be shared here.
Investigations: We may investigate and disclose information from or about you if we have a good faith belief that such investigation or disclosure is (a) reasonably necessary to comply with legal process and law enforcement instructions and orders, such as a search warrant, subpoena, statute, judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us; (b) helpful to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site; or (c) protect our rights, reputation, property, or that of our users, affiliates, or the public.
Links: The Site may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. Except as set forth herein, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all such third party websites.
Facebook and Twitter: If you are logged into Facebook, and you access but are not logged into the Site, we may receive information from Facebook to make it easier for you to create an account on the Site and show you relevant content from your Facebook friends. This information personalises your experience and helps you create a Good Gym Guide account. You can also connect your Good Gym Guide account to your accounts on third party services like Facebook or Twitter, in which case we may collect and store information identifying your account with the third party service. We use the information to help you connect and share public content with your friends and followers. You can manage these settings here.
4. Controlling Your Personal Data
Other users may be able to identify you, or associate you with your account if you include personal information in the content you post publicly. You can reduce the risk of being personally identified by using the Site pseudonymously, though doing so could detract from the credibility of your contributions to the Site.
Please also note that the messages you send or receive using the Site are only private to the extent that both you and the sender/recipient keep them private. For example, we do not have any control over whether a recipient of one of your messages publicly posts it or its contents. Similarly, Good Gym Guide may also access such messages in the course of investigations relating to Site use.
5. Data Retention and Account Termination
You can close your account by clicking here. We will remove your public posts from view and/or dissociate them from your account profile, but we may retain information about you for the purposes authorised under this Privacy Policy unless prohibited by law. For example, we may retain information to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site or to comply with legal obligations. Please note that businesses cannot remove their business listings, ratings or reviews by closing their accounts.
6. Children
The Site is intended for general audiences and is not directed to children under 14. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 14. If you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information without parental consent, please contact us here. If we become aware that a child under 14 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.
7. Security
We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
8. Dispute Resolution
If you believe that Good Gym Guide has not adhered to this Privacy Policy you may contact us online by clicking here
9. Jurisdiction
The information we obtain from or about you may be processed and stored in Australia, which may provide for different data protection rules than the country in which you reside. We comply with The Privacy Act as set forth by the Australian Government regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the Commonwealth of Australia. We will respond to requests relating to personal data within 30 days.
10. Modifications to This Privacy Policy
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will govern our use of information about you. By continuing to access or use the Site after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
Advertisement
